Finding Aid for the Tony Barrett Papers PASC.0061
UCLA Library Special Collections
Tony Barrett papers
1929-1975
UCLA Library Special Collections
PASC.0061
70.5 linear feet (137 boxes and 65 volumes)
Tony Barrett was a talented writer and producer who contributed to a variety of radio, television, and motion pictures projects. Among those projects were: The Mod Squad, Burke's Law, Felony Squad, Peter Gunn, and the Snoop Sisters. The collection consists of scripts and production material related to his career.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Steffi Barrett; 1975, 1980.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 995558743606533
Biography
Tony Barrett was born Martin Lefkowitz on May 24, 1916 in New York, New York. He was married to writer Steffi Barrett, nee Nordli. The multi-talented Barrett was a radio and screen actor, screenwriter and television writer and producer. Among his numerous credits are The Mod Squad, Burke's Law, Felony Squad, Peter Gunn, and the Snoop Sisters. He died of cancer in Los Angeles, CA, November 16, 1974.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of material related to the career of producer and writer, Tony Barrett. Includes scripts, production material, notes, and correspondence. Contains material for approximately 70 television series and motion pictures, including The Mod Squad, Burke's Law, Felony Squad, Peter Gunn, and Snoop Sisters. There are also scripts from approximately 80 radio shows that Barrett acted in, wrote for, or both, including Dangerous Assignment, Lux Radio Theatre, and Suspense. It also includes bound volumes of scripts.
Arrangement
Arranged in the following series: 1. Television and motion picture scripts and production material; 2. Radio scripts and production material; 3. Unproduced script material, clippings, and correspondence; 4. Bound scripts.
Radio writers -- Archives.; Television producers and directors -- Archives.; Television writers -- Archives.; Scripts (documents).; Barrett, Tony,1916-1974--Archives.
- Series 1. Television and motion picture scripts and production material
  - 77 Sunset Strip (ABC, 1958-1964)
    - THE FUMBLE by Tony Barrett, 1963 (Box 127, Folders 4-5)
      Scope and Contents
      Includes notes.
    - Notes, undated (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - THE TARGET by Tony Barrett, 1963 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - 88 BARS by Tony Barrett, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - 88 BARS by Tony Barrett, 1963 September 10 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - THE TOY JUNGLE by Tony Barrett and Louis Vittes from a story by Tony Barrett, 1963 October 17 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - NOT SUCH A SIMPLE KNOT by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - NOT SUCH A SIMPLE KNOT by Tony Barrett, 1963 December 2 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - THE TARGET by Tony Barrett, 1963 December 12 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - TOY JUNGLE, undated (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - TOY JUNGLE by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Action in the Afternoon (CBS, 1953-1954)
    - Scripts 1-5, undated (Box 123, Folders 3-5)
      Though there are three volumes each containing "Scripts 1-5," the stories are all different, so there are actually fifteen unique scripts.
  - The Adventures of Rin Tin Tin (ABC, 1954-1959)
    - RIN TIN TIN AND THE LAST CHANCE outline by Tony Barrett and Paul Pierce, undated (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - RIN TIN TIN MEETS MR. PRESIDENT by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 120, Folder 6)
      Also includes RIN TIN TIN AND THE SACRED LANCE by Douglas Heyes and Roy Irwin, 1954 August 20 and RIN TIN TIN AND THE LAST CHANCE, undated.
  - Batman (ABC, 1966-1968)
    - Pilot script by Lorenzo Semple, Jr., 1965 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Behind Closed Doors (NBC, 1958-1959)
    - MIGHTIER THAN THE SWORD by Robert Leslie Bellem and Tony Barrett, 1959 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - The Black Eye (unrealized)
    - Script pages and notes, undated (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Notes, undated (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - THE LOOT OF ALL EVIL outlines and notes, undated (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - THE LOOT OF ALL EVIL by Tony Barrett, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      Includes series concept by Rose H. Schulter.
    - THE LOOT OF ALL EVIL by Tony Barrett, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - THE LOOT OF ALL EVIL by Tony Barrett, 1970 October 13 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - The Bob Cummings Show (CBS, 1961-1962)
    - YUCATAN STORY by Sheldon Stark, 1961 April 14 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      Probably broadcast as VERY WARM FOR MAYAN. Also includes writers' guide.
  - Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre (NBC, 1963-1967)
    - TO SLEEP, PERCHANCE TO SCREAM by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      Includes note, call sheet.
    - TO SLEEP, PERCHANCE TO SCREAM by Tony Barrett, 1967 March 1 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - TO SLEEP, PERCHANCE TO SCREAM by Tony Barrett, 1967 March 14 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Boots and Saddles (Syndicated, 1957-1959)
    - Story lines, undated (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - THE RECRUIT [empty folder], undated (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - QUIET DAY AT CAMP LOWELL [empty folder], undated (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - POUND OF FLESH notes and script pages, undated (Box 95, Folder 5)
      Includes copies of two letters to Het Mannheim.
    - Story briefs/outlines [empty folder], undated (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - THE OBSESSION by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Research material, undated (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - ONE-MAN WAR by Tony Barrett, 1957 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - THE OBSESSION by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - THE DECISION [empty folder], undated (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - PRIVATE WAR [empty folder], undated (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - POUND OF FLESH by Tony Barrett, 1957 September 12 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - THE RECRUIT by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Bracken's World (NBC, 1969-1970)
    - JENNY, WHO BOMBS BUILDINGS by George Kirgo, 1970 June 19 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Burke's Law (ABC, 1963-1966)
    - A VERY IMPORTANT RUSSIAN IS MISSING by Tony Barrett from a story by Tony Barrett and Samuel A. Peeples, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      Includes treatment and notes.
    - THE WEAPON by Tony Barrett, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - A LITTLE GIFT FOR CAIRO By Ben Starr and Tony Barrett from a story by Ben Starr, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Notes and story ideas, undated (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - WHO KILLED INA FINGREE? notes and fragments, undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - WHO KILLED THE RABBIT'S HUSBAND? outlines, undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Notes and story ideas, undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - NIGHTMARE IN THE SUN script pages and notes, undated (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - WHO KILLED THE SURF BROAD? by Tony Barrett, 1964 July 10 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - THE WEAPON by Tony Barrett, 1965 June 7 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - NIGHTMARE IN THE SUN by Tony Barrett, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - A LITTLE GIFT FOR CAIRO by Tony Barrett from a story by Ben Starr, 1965 September 22 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - A VERY IMPORTANT RUSSIAN IS MISSING by Tony Barrett from a story by Tony Barrett and Samuel A. Peeples, 1965 November 1 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Outlines, 1963-1964 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - WHO KILLED MY GIRL? by Tony Barrett, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - WHO KILLED THE HORNE OF PLENTY? outline, 1964 May 12 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - WHO KILLED THE TALL ONE IN THE MIDDLE? by Tony Barrett, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - WHO KILLED THE SWINGER ON THE HOOK? by Tony Barrett, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - WHO KILLED THE SURF BROAD? by Tony Barrett, 1964 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - WHO KILLED THE TALL ONE IN THE MIDDLE?, 1964 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - WHO KILLED MR. COLBY IN LADIES' LINGERIE? by Tony Barrett, 1964-1965 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      Includes notes and contracts.
    - WHO KILLED THE RABBIT'S HUSBAND? by Tony Barrett, 1965 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - WHO KILLED THE HORNE OF PLENTY?, undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - WHO KILLED ROSIE SUNSET? notes, undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - WHO KILLED MY GIRL?, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - WHO KILLED BILLY JOE?, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - WHO KILLED ANNIE FORAN?, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - WHO KILLED WHAT'S HIS NAME?, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - WHO KILLED MARTY KELSO? by Tony Barrett, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - A LITTLE GIFT FOR CAIRO by Tony Barrett from a story by Ben Starr, 1965 September 22 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - DIAMONDS ARE A MAN'S BEST FRIEND by Ben Starr, 1965 July 27 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      This could be an early draft of A LITTLE GIFT FOR CAIRO.
    - MORE DEADLY THAN THE MALE by Edmund H. North, 1965 May 12 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      Probably unrealized, with no connection to the episode DEADLIER THAN THE MALE.
    - NIGHTMARE IN THE SUN by Tony Barrett, 1965 August 23 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - A VERY IMPORTANT RUSSIAN IS MISSING by Tony Barrett from a story by Samuel A. Peeples, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - NIGHTMARE IN THE SUN by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Bus Stop (ABC, 1961-1962)
    - COUNTY GENERAL by David Shaw, 1962 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - The Californians (NBC, 1957-1959)
    - LITTLE LOST MAN by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Casablanca (ABC, 1955-1956)
    - THE OBSESSION by Tony Barrett, 1955 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - THE MERCHANDISE outlines by Tony Barrett from a story by Jerome C. Robinson, 1955 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - WHO HOLDS TOMORROW? by Dave P. Harmon, 1955 May 31 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Casey Jones (Syndicated, 1957-1958)
    - SPUR LINE TO DANGER by Tony Barrett, 1957 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Colt .45 (ABC, 1957-1960)
    - THE HUNT outline by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Outline by Tony Barrett, 1957-1958 (Box 120, Folder 7)
      Includes rejection letter.
    - Notes and outlines, undated (Box 121, Folder 7)
      Includes material on several other shows as well.
  - The Count of Monte Cristo (ITV, 1956)
    - THE DE BERRY AFFAIR by Roger Clay, 1955 August 17 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - THE ART OF TERROR by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - THE ART OF TERROR, undated (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Crusader (CBS, 1955-1956)
    - ONE-WAY TRAIN by Oscar Millard, 1955 March 2 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Dan Raven (NBC, 1960-1961)
    - THE BOBBY DARIN STORY contract, 1960 July 1 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - THE BOBBY DARIN STORY by Lewis Reed and Tony Barrett, 1960 July 7 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      General
      Probably broadcast as THE HIGH COST OF FAME.
    - THE MECHANIC by Tony Barrett and Lewis Reed, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - THE NIGHT IS NUMBERED by Lewis Reed and Tony Barrett, 1960 June 27 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - THE MECHANIC by Tony Barrett and Lewis Reed, 1960 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - The Dick Powell Show (NBC,1961-1963)
    - TISSUE OF HATE by Tony Barrett, 1962 November 6 (Box 89, Folder 2)
      Also includes script GOODBYE HANNAH by Aaron Spelling from a story by Steve Fisher, 1961 August 15.
  - The Doctor (NBC, 1952-1953)
    - SCRIPT #1 by Harry Ruskin, 1955 March 2 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Doctor Mike (CBS, 1959)
    - Script pages, 1956 November 20 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - DOCTOR MIKE by Benedict Berenberg, 1956 October 23 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Dragnet (NBC, 1951-1959)
    - THE BIG CHET, undated (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - THE BIG STEAL, 1956 April 4 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - The Family Tree (unrealized)
    - Treatment for a daytime serial by Steffi Barrett, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Also includes: correspondence; clippings; "A Federal Source Book: Answers to the Most Frequently Asked Questions about Drugs."
    - Screenplay by Steffi Barrett, undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Treatments and script pages by Steffi Barrett, undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Faraday and Company (NBC, 1973-1974)
    - Test screening report, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      Mis-labeled Snoop Sisters.
    - A WHEELBARROW FULL OF TROUBLE by Burt Prelutsky and Jimmy Sangster, 1973 (Box 52, Folders 1-2)
      Includes correspondence.
    - Budgets and publicity, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      Includes book Whatever Happened to...? by Marcia Seligson, Mort Gerberg, and Avery Corman with a special tie-in cover.
    - FIRE AND ICE production documents, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      Also includes story ideas.
    - A WHEELBARROW FULL OF TROUBLE by Jimmy Sangster, Tony Barrett, Leonard Stern, and Burt Prelutsky, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - FIRE AND ICE by Robert W. Lenski, 1973 (Box 52, Folders 6-7)
    - A WHEELBARROW FULL OF TROUBLE production documents, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - FIRE AND ICE production documents, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - KELSO treatment by Edward J. Lasko, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Also includes A WHEELBARROW FULL OF TROUBLE production documents and script pages for reshoots.
    - Editing notes, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Also includes notes for Mod Squad and Snoop Sisters.
    - FIRE AND ICE by Robert W. Lenski, 1973 September 19 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - A MATTER OF MAGIC by William Clark and Robert Foster from a story by William Clark, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Includes production documents.
    - A MATTER OF MAGIC by Ed Lasko, Tony Barrett, Robert Foster, and Burt Prelutsky, 1973 (Box 53, Folders 3-7)
    - A MATTER OF MAGIC by Burt Prelutsky, 1973 September 21 (Box 53, Folders 8-9)
    - A MATTER OF MAGIC by Ed Lasko, Tony Barrett, Robert Foster, and Burt Prelutsky, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - FIRE AND ICE by Robert W. Lenski, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - A WHEELBARROW FULL OF TROUBLE by Jimmy Sangster, Tony Barrett, Leonard Stern, and Burt Prelutsky, 1973 (Box 53a, Folders 1-2)
    - A MATTER OF MAGIC by William Clark and Robert Foster from a story by William Clark, 1973 (Box 53a, Folders 3-4)
    - FIRE AND ICE by Robert W. Lenski, 1973 (Box 53a, Folders 5-6)
    - Director's status reports, 1973 (Box 53a, Folder 7)
      Also includes reports for Snoop Sisters.
    - A MATTER OF MAGIC correspondence and production documents, 1973 (Box 53a, Folder 8)
    - A WHEELBARROW FULL OF TROUBLE by Jimmy Sangster, 1973 (Folder 54, Folder 1)
      Also includes an outline by Frank Telford.
    - A WHEELBARROW FULL OF TROUBLE by Jimmy Sangster, Tony Barrett, Leonard Stern, and Burt Prelutsky, 1973 (Folder 54, Folder 2)
    - FIRE AND ICE by Robert W. Lenski, 1973 September 7 (Folder 54, Folder 3)
    - A WHEELBARROW FULL OF TROUBLE by Jimmy Sangster, Tony Barrett, Leonard Stern, and Burt Prelutsky, 1973 (Folder 54, Folders 4-10)
  - The Felony Squad (ABC 1966-1969)
    - WHO'LL TAKE CARE OF JOEY? by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - THE 30-GRAM KILL by Tony Barrett from a story by Don Tait and William Koenig, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - THE FEAR MERCHANT by Tony Barrett from a story by Quentin Sparr, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - TARGET! by Tony Barrett and Frank L. Moss from a story by Frank L. Moss, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - THE STRANGLER by Tony Barrett from a story by Tony Barrett and Lee Irwin, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - THE PAT HAND OF DEATH by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - LET HIM DIE! by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - THE IMMACULATE KILLER by Alfred Brenner and Philip Saltzman from a story by Alfred Brenner, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - A BLUEPRINT FOR DYING by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - THE DEATH BAG by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - DEADLY FUSE by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - THE 30-GRAM KILL, undated (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - WHO'LL TAKE CARE OF JOEY? by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - THE STRANGLER by Tony Barrett, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - THE BLOODSUCKERS by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
      Includes notes. Also includes script THE FEAR MERCHANT by Franklin Barton.
    - TARGET! by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 70, Folder 7)
      Includes notes. Also includes outline and script THE FATAL RECKONING by Frank L. Moss and WGA credit arbitration letter.
    - A BLUEPRINT FOR DYING by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - THE PAT HAND OF DEATH by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Story ideas, undated (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - THE PAT HAND OF DEATH by Tony Barrett, 1967 August 8 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - THE FEAR MERCHANT by Tony Barrett from a story by Quentin Sparr, 1967 February 6 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - THE DEATH BAG by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - LET HIM DIE! by Tony Barrett, 1967 June 26 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - THE 30-GRAM KILL by Tony Barrett from a story by Don Tait and William Koenig, 1967 July 7 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - TARGET! by Tony Barrett and Frank L. Moss from a story by Frank L. Moss, 1967 January 11 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - A BLUEPRINT FOR DYING by Tony Barrett, 1967 February 1 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - MISS REILLY'S REVENGE by George Eckstein and Leonard Kantor from a story by Leonard Kantor, 1966 August 23 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - BETWEEN TWO FIRES by Howard Gast, 1966 October 3 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - THE PRO AND THE CON by Norman Katkov, 1966 July 13 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - THE TERROR TRAP by Alvin Boretz, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - LUCK OUT! by Donald S. Sanford, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - A WALK TO OBLIVION script pages, 1966 July 27 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - STRIKEOUT script pages, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - TARGET! by Tony Barrett and Frank L. Moss from a story by Frank L. Moss, 1967 January 11 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - THE STRANGLER by Tony Barrett from a story by Tony Barrett and Lee Irwin, 1966 December 13 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - A BLUEPRINT FOR DYING by Tony Barrett, 1967 January 30 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - THE FEAR MERCHANT by Tony Barrett from a story by Quentin Sparr, undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - THE KILLER INSTINCT by Mann Rubin, 1966 October 20 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - A DEATH FOR A DEATH by Donald S. Sanford from a story by Donald S. Sanford and Harry Kronman, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - THE DEADLY PARTNER by Donald S. Sanford, 1966 October 26 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - THE NIGHT OF THE SHARK by Howard Gast, 1966 November 23 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - THE IMMACULATE KILLER by Alfred Brenner and Philip Staltzman from a story by Alfred Brenner, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - PROLOGUE TO MURDER by John Kneubuhl, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - A PENNY GAME, A TWO-BIT MURDER by Adrian Spies, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - LIVE COWARD, DEAD HERO by Franklin Barton and Jay Simms from a story by Jay Simms, 1967 January 24 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - THE STREETS ARE FILLED WITH QUICKSAND by Harold Gast, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - THE DEATH OF A DREAM by Adrian Spies, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - ECHO OF A KILLING by Dan Ullman, 1967 January 18 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - DEBT OF FEAR by John Furia, Jr., 1967 January 6 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - BREAKOUT by Barry Oringer, 1966 December 6 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Flight (Syndicated, 1958-1959)
    - THE HARD WAY by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - BORDER INCIDENT by Tony Barrett, 1958 (Box 124, Folder 2)
      Also includes THE HARD WAY by Tony Barrett, 1958 September 4.
  - The Ford Television Theatre (NBC, 1952-1956; ABC, 1956-1957)
    - SITTING DUCK by Tony Barrett, 1957 March 21 (Box 94, Folder 10)
      Probably broadcast as ADVENTURE FOR HIRE.
    - SITTING DUCK by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - SITTING DUCK, undated (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - FOUR YARDS by Tony Barrett, 1956 April 10 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Front Row Center (CBS, 1955-1956)
    - DINNER AT EIGHT by Whitfield Cook from the play by George S. Kaufman and Edna Ferber, 1955 June 1 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Garrison's Gorillas (ABC, 1967-1968)
    - BANKER'S HOURS by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - BLACK MARKET by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Notes, undated (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - WAR AND CRIME notes, undated (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - WAR AND CRIME (PART I) by William R. Yates from a story by Tony Barrett, 1967 December 8 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - WAR AND CRIME (PART II) by William R. Yates from a story by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - THE GREAT THEFT by Norman Hudis, 1967 May 31 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - BANKER'S HOURS by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - The Girl from U.N.C.L.E. (NBC, 1966-1967)
    - THE DOG-GONE AFFAIR by Tony Barrett, 1966 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - THE KILLER WAVE AFFAIR by Tony Barrett, 1967 February 1 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      Broadcast as THE U.N.C.L.E. SAMURAI AFFAIR.
    - THE DOG-GONE AFFAIR by Tony Barrett, 1966 June 29 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Notes and story ideas, undated (Box 78, Folders 1-2)
    - THE ROMANY LIE AFFAIR by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - THE KILLER WAVE AFFAIR by Tony Barrett, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - THE HORNS-OF-THE-DILEMMA AFFAIR by Tony Barrett, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - THE DOG-GONE AFFAIR by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - THE ROMANY LIE AFFAIR by Tony Barrett, 1966 September 22 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - THE HORNS-OF-THE-DILEMMA AFFAIR by Tony Barrett, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - THE KILLER WAVE AFFAIR by Tony Barrett, 1966-1967 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Good Times (Columbia, 1967)
    - First draft screenplay by Nick Hyams, 1966 January 11 (Folder 55, Folder 1)
    - Opening script pages, undated (Folder 55, Folder 2)
    - Final white screenplay by Tony Barrett, 1966 February 28 (Folder 55, Folders 3-4)
    - Screenplay by Tony Barrett, undated (Folder 55, Folder 5)
    - Screenplay, undated (Folder 55, Folder 6)
    - Screenplays by Tony Barrett, 1966 (Folder 55, Folder 7)
      Includes notes and two letters from Barrett's agent.
  - The Guns of Will Sonnett (ABC, 1967-1969)
    - THE SECRET OF HANGTOWN MINE by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - THE SECRET OF HANGTOWN MINE by Tony Barrett, 1967 August 10 (Box 120, Folder 10)
      Also includes outlines for other westerns.
  - Gunsmoke (CBS, 1955-1975)
    - THE WAKE, undated (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Hellcats (unrealized)
    - YANKEE, FLY HOME by W.R. Burnett and Tony Barrett, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - YANKEE, FLY HOME by W.R. Burnett and Tony Barrett from a story by W.R. Burnett, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Highway Patrol (Syndicated 1955-1959)
    - Outline by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Script by Tony Barrett, 1955 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      Includes notes. Broadcast as ANTI-TOXIN.
    - 32B by Tony Barrett, 1955 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Honey West (ABC, 1965-1966)
    - THE ABOMINABLE SNOWMAN outline and notes by Gwen Bagni and Paul Dubov, 1965-1966 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      Includes: additional story ideas; outline by William Bast; air date schedule; series format outline.
    - SLAY, GYPSY, SLAY by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - LIKE VISIONS AND OMENS AND ALL THAT JAZZ by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - DIAL "M" FOR MONSTER notes and outlines, undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - LIVE A LITTLE...KILL A LITTLE by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - A MATTER OF WIFE AND DEATH by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - A MILLION BUCKS IN ANYBODY'S LANGUAGE by Tony Barrett, 1965 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - A NICE LITTLE TILL TO TAP by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - LIKE VISIONS AND OMENS AND ALL THAT JAZZ by Tony Barrett, 1965 December 15 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - A MATTER OF WIFE AND DEATH by Tony Barrett, 1965 August 3 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - LIVE A LITTLE...KILL A LITTLE by Tony Barrett, 1965 May 25 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - A NICE LITTLE TILL TO TAP by Tony Barrett, 1965 October 22 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - A MATTER OF WIFE AND DEATH by Tony Barrett, 1965 August 3 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - LIKE VISIONS AND OMENS AND ALL THAT JAZZ by Tony Barrett, 1965 December 6 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - SLAY, GYPSY, SLAY by Tony Barrett, 1966 January 18 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - If I Love You Am I Trapped Forever? (CBS, 1974)
    - Pilot episode by Larry Gelbart based on the novel by M.E. Kerr, 1973 December 20 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - If Tomorrow Comes (ABC, 1971)